We were wondering what was taking so long...
...but now we understand. You were doing this.
Okay. I wanted to surprise you, but....
For your housewarming gift,
I got you a baby chick and a baby duck.
Really? You got us a chick and a duck?
Oh, great.
Just what you want for
a new house with infants. Bird feces!
But they must've jumped off the table.
Now they're gone!
Don't worry, we'll find them.
Actually, I'm gonna go check on the twins.
Oh, God! What did I just step on?
It's okay. It's just an egg roll.
You stepped on my egg roll?!
I'm sorry.
I didn't know to look for Chinese food on the floor.
Just put it on a plate and leave.
- Okay. Let's find these birds. - All right.
Wait, wait. You hear that?
They're in the table!
Well, that can't be good.
- We gotta get them out of there! - How?
Maybe we can lure them out. You know any birdcalls?
Oh, tons. I'm quite the woodsman.
Well, maybe we can just tip the table a little.
Joey, wait! The ball!
So, what do we do?
Maybe we can open this up somehow.
Okay.
No. It's all glued together.
Does that mean we have to bust it open?
- I don't know. Maybe. - Oh, my God.
I know. It's-- It's the foosball table.
All right, you know what? We don't have a choice.
It's like I would have said in that sci-fi movie
if I'd have gotten the part.
Those are our men in there, and we have to get them out...
...even if I have to sacrifice the most important thing in my life...
...my time machine.
- Did that movie ever get made? - It did not.
Ross, where are you going?
To talk to Rachel.
Isn't that why we took a ride in the death cab?
You're walking up to her at the gate?
Have you never chased anyone through the airport before?
Not since my cop show got canceled.
You have to get a ticket to get past security.
What? We're never gonna make it.
Not with that attitude. Now, haul ass!
Okay, if you could all walk slower,
that'd be great.
- Madame, your passport, please. - Oh, my God.
I was afraid I wouldn't remember my high school French.
But I understood every word you just said.
- Your boarding pass, please. - Oh, sure.
Shoot, I had it. Oh, I can't believe this.
Madame, if you don't have your--
I have it, I have it!
Okay, I can't find it,
but I remember that I was in seat 32C...
...because that's my bra size.
Madame. You must have your boarding pass--
Ok, fine. But you know what?
If I was in 36D, we would not be having this problem.
- Hi. I need a ticket. - Just one?
I drive you here,
and I don't get to see how it works out?
Fine. Two tickets. I need two tickets.
We're on our honeymoon.
And the destination?
I don't care. Whatever's the cheapest.
I'm so lucky I married you.
Oh, shoot. Damn it. Where is it?
I found it. I found it. I told you I would find it.
In your face. You're a different person.
Sorry.
Okay. Flight 421, Paris.
I don't see it. Do you see it?
No. Did we miss it?
No, no, it's impossible. It doesn't leave for another 20 minutes.
Maybe we have the flight number wrong.
God.
- Hello. - Hey, it's me. Here's Ross.
What?
Hey. Hey, listen--
You wouldn't believe the cute noises the twins are making.
Wait, listen.
But Monica--
Monica...
I'm sorry. They were doing it before.
That's all right. Listen, listen.
Oh, wait, wait. Here they go again.
Monica...
- Monica? - Isn't that cute?
That is precious! Listen....
I need Rachel's flight information.
Oh, okay.
All right, it's flight 421. Leaves at 8:40.
Yes, that's what I had . It's not on the board.
That's what it says here.
Flight 421. Leaves at 8:40. Newark Airport.
- What? - Newark Airport.
Why? Where are you?
JFK.
Don't worry, you guys!
We're gonna get you out of there!
And we're also gonna buy you tiny bird hearing aids.
Okay. Here goes.
What's the matter?
I need to say goodbye to the table first.
I understand.
Okay.
Table...
...you have given us so many great times.
And you guys, Jordan, Victor, Joel....
All of you guys. What can I say?
You guys make us look good.
- You want to say anything? - I don't know.
Except that, for one last time....
Good game...
Good game.
Okay. Here we go.
I can't do it.
Well, I can't do it either.
Hey. Did you find them?
Yeah. They're stuck inside the table.
And we have to bust it open, but neither of us can do it.
Oh, well, sure. It's got to be so hard.
I'll do it. Give me.
Phoebe!
No, no, no!
Wow, I've never gone this fast before.
Phoebe, forget it, okay?
Newark is, like, an hour away.
There's no way we'll make it in time.
She's got her cell. You could call her.
I am not doing this over the phone.
You don't have any other choice.
- Hello? - Rachel. Oh, good.
By the way, did you just get on the plane?
- Yeah. - For what is worse, we would have caught her...
...if we were at the right airport.
- Rachel, hang on. - No. No. No.
Phoebe, is everything okay?
Actually, no. No. You have to get off the plane.
- What? Why? - I have this feeling that...
...something's wrong with it.
Something is wrong with the left phalange.
Oh, honey, I'm sure there's nothing wrong with the plane.
Look, I have to go.
I love you, and l will call you the minute I get to Paris.
What was that?
Oh, that was just my crazy friend.
She told me to get off the plane
because she had a "feeling" that there...
...was something wrong with the left phalange.
Okay. That doesn't sound good.
Oh, I wouldn't worry about it.
She comes up with this stuff,
and she's almost never right.
But she is sometimes.
Well....
What are you doing?
I can't take this plane now.
Excuse me, sir. Where are you going?
I have to get off this plane.
Her friend has a feeling
something's wrong with the left phalange.
Could I get some peanuts?
What's wrong with the plane?
There's nothing wrong.
The left phalange.
There's no "phalange."
Oh, my God. This plane doesn't even have a phalange.
- I'm not flying on it. - Ma'am. Please sit down.
What's going on?
We're getting off. There is no phalange!
This is ridiculous. I--
Yeah, okay.
All right. My job here is done.
That was impressive.
Yeah. You didn't even use the tools for most of it.
Yeah, they were just slowing me down.
All right. I gotta get back to the babies.
See you girls later.
- Sorry about the table, man. - Yeah.
You gonna buy a new one?
Probably not. No.
I don't know how much I'm gonna want to play
after you go.
- At least we got these little guys out. - Yeah.
We were worried about you.
I guess I better get used to things
crapping in my hand, huh?
I'm gonna miss these little guys.
It was nice having birds around again.
Hey, you know what?
Maybe we should keep them here with you.
What?
Yeah. We got a lot going on right now.
And plus, here, they'd have their own room.
I could get a goose!
You know, I think you're set with the poultry.
Thanks, man. You hear that, you guys?
You're gonna get to stay here.
And it's good...
...you know, because....
Because now you have a reason
to come visit.
I think there may be another reason.
So....
Awkward hug or lame cool-guy handshake?
Yeah, well, you know,
lame cool-guy handshake.
Ma'am, I assure you, the plane is fine.
And you fixed the phalange?
Yes. The phalange's fixed.
As a matter of fact,
we've put a whole lot of extra phalanges onboard,
just in case.
- Where is she? - I don't see her.
- Rachel! Rachel Green! - There she is!
Rachel! Rachel!
Whoa, do you have a boarding pass?
No. I just have to talk to someone.
I'm sorry. You need a boarding pass.
- No, no. But you don't-- - Rachel!
What? Oh, my God.
What are you guys doing here?
Okay. You're on.
What? What, Ross?
Okay, you're scaring me. What's going on?
- Okay. Thing is.... - Yeah.
- Don't go. - What?
Please, please stay with me.
I am so in love with you. Please don't go.
- Oh, my God. - I know. I know.
I shouldn't have waited till now to say it,
but-- That was stupid, okay? I'm sorry.
But I'm telling you now.
I love you.
Do not get on this plane.
Miss, are you boarding the plane?
Hey, hey.
I know you love me. I know you do.
- Miss. - I....
l.... I have to get on the plane.
- No, you don't. - Yes, I do.
- No, you don't. I do. - They're waiting for me, Ross.
I can't do this right now,
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Rachel.
I'm so sorry.
I really thought she'd stay.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Well, that's it.
Everything's packed.
This is weird.
I know.
Yeah.
Does this mean there's nothing to eat?
I put three lasagnas in your freezer.
I love you.
Hey.
Hey. Did you guys make it in time?
Yeah, yeah.
He talked to her, but she got on the plane anyway.
Where's Ross?
He went home. He didn't want to see anybody.
Ross. Hi, it's me.
I just got back on the plane,
and I just feel awful.
That is so not how I wanted
things to end with us.
It's just that I wasn't expecting
to see you.
And all of a sudden you're there
and saying these things.
Now I'm just sitting here
and thinking...
...of all the stuff I should have said
and I didn't.
I mean, I didn't even get to tell you
that I love you too.
Because of course I do. I love you.
I love you.
What am I doing? I love you.
I've got to see you.
I've got to get off this plane.
Oh, my God.
Okay, excuse me.
Miss, please sit down.
No, I'm sorry. I'm really sorry,
but I need to get off the plane.
I need to tell someone that I love them.
Miss, I can't let you off.
Let her off the plane!
I am afraid you are gonna have to take a seat.
Oh, please, Miss. You don't understand.
Try to understand!
Come on, miss, isn't there any way
that you can just let me off the--?
No! No!
Oh, my God. Did she get off the plane?
Did she get off the plane?
I got off the plane.
You got off the plane.
I do love you.
I love you too,
and I am never letting you go again.
Okay. Because this is where I want to be.
No more messing around.
I don't want to mess this up again.
Me neither. We're done being stupid.
Okay. It's you and me, all right? This is it.
This is it. Unless we're on a break.
Don't make jokes now.
Okay, please be careful with that.
It was my grandmother's. Be careful.
Thank you.
If that falls off the truck,
it wouldn't be the worst thing.
I know.
Seems smaller somehow.
Has it always been purple?
Look around, you guys.
This was your first home.
And it was a happy place,
filled with love and laughter.
But more important,
because of rent control, it was a frigging steal.
Hey, do you realize that, at one time or another,
we all lived in this apartment?
Oh, yeah. That's true.
I haven't.
What about that summer during college
that you lived with Grandma...
...and you tried to make it as a dancer?
Do you realize we almost made it 10 years
without that coming up?
Oh, honey, I forgot.
I promised Treeger that we'd leave our keys.
Oh, okay.
- So I guess this is it. - Yeah.
I guess so.
This is harder than I thought it would be.
Oh, it's gonna be okay.
Come on.
Do you guys have to go to the new house now,
or do you have some time?
We got some time.
- Okay. Should we get some coffee? - Sure.
Where?